# PRAJYOT HALDANKAR

#### **Business Analyst**

Business Analyst with over 2 years of experience in Financial Services (Mutual Fund) and software development organizations. I bring together unconventional thinking, unique experiences, and approaches to clearly communicate solutions to complex business problems. Aiming to utilize my strong prioritization skills and analytical ability to achieve the goals.



# **About Me**



7 years experience



October 01, 1989



🕽 Navi Mumbai, Maharashtra



+91 76660 51261



talktoprajyot@gmail.com



# **Education**

#### **Bachelor of Commerce**

Rashtriya Vishwa Vidyapeeth Mumbai Navi Mumbai, Maharashtra

Graduated, June 2011 Marks 65 %



# Work Experience



January 2017 - Current

#### Accord Fintech Pvt. Ltd. - (Business Analyst)

Navi Mumbai, Maharashtra

- Re-engineering entire Client On-boarding process to make it paperless by integrating it with the system of Govt Registered Certified KYC Agency CVL-KRA.
- Integration of the platform with online Mutual Fund Transaction system of Bombay Stock Exchange, enabling real-time execution and payments for the purchase of mutual funds.
- Involved in monthly revenue reconciliation and documentation of the process to built it on the online platform to eliminate all the possible human errors which resulted due to a huge volume of transactions.
- Preparing the Understanding document and FSD (Functional Specification Documents)
- Bug tracking and resolution of the application related issue.
- Managing IFA servicing team involved in providing training and addressing the issues faced by the IFA users.
- Functional Testing of the entire platform.
- Communicate the client's business requirements by constructing easy-to-understand data and process models.
- Liaise between business and technical personnel to ensure a mutual understanding of processes and applications.
- Elicitation of Business Requirements with the vendor and internal users from different functions of wealth management business.
- To document the business process by identifying the requirements.
- Responsible for training of the new resources in the support staff.
- To make the Test plan for the testing team.



February 2016 - December 2016

#### **SPH HR Solutions - (Executive Operations)**

Navi Mumbai, Maharashtra

- Handling entire Operational Activities.
- Preparing Invoices and sending to clients for payment.
- Co-coordinating with clients for feedbacks.
- Preparing various types of letters and reports.



August 2013 - January 2016

#### Gemini Power Hydraulics Pvt. Ltd. - (Executive Operations)

Mumbai, Maharashtra

- Co-coordinating with Sales team for preparing quotation through Business Pulse Software.
- Identifying areas of Business Improvement.
- Developing maps and flowcharts of current and future business processes.
- Reporting on the likely impact of process modifications.
- Flagging up potential problems at an early stage.
- Developing a clear understanding of existing business functions and processes.
- Preparing PowerPoint presentations and Excel Spreadsheet for business meetings.



April 2011 - September 2012

#### People Interactive India Pvt. Ltd. - (Customer Relationship Officer)

Mumbai, Maharashtra

- Manage all customer requirements and queries and solve their problems swiftly.
- Responsible to provide information to members via Phone, Live chat and Emails.
- Periodical review of work training for staff to overcome weak areas.
- Screening and activating new profiles as per the content.
- Identifies opportunities for operational efficiency.



### **Skills**

- Knowledge in project and operations management and re-engineering theory.
- Strong in business analysis and client relationship.
- Possess problem-solving and decision-making skills.
- Ability to bring out the best in pressure situations from the team.
- Translating and simplifying requirements
- Requirement Gathering and Gap Analysis
- Software Functional Testing



# Languages

- English • •
- Hindi ● ●
- Marathi • •



- Playing Football & Cricket.
- Volunteering for a social cause.



# **Personal Details**

Fathers Name: Mr. Sudhakar Haldankar Single Marital Status: Birthday: October 01, 1989 Nationality: Indian

Gender: Male

Address: B-1102, Sujata Empress CHSL, Plot No - 50, Sector - 35/D, Kharghar

Navi Mumbai - 410210, Maharashtra.

### **References Available on Request**



# **Declaration**

I do hereby declare that above particulars of information and facts stated are true, correct and complete to the best of my knowledge and belief.

Place:	
Date:	(Prajyot Haldankar)